This is your dad
Isn't this your dad?
It's a piece
Yes
Chemo, huh
Here
[Maddening laughter]
Hahaha
No
Meant to be
Mine is called
Uh, spilling cup
Hahahaha
Splashed everywhere
I, the young master, want you
Hahaha
Please don't
Bear biscuits
I'll charge the ice crystal
At your disposal
Oh
It's like this
Seeing this moment,
I felt the hatred dissolve.
An eye for an eye...
when will it end?
And you're the one leading?
Bro
Look at those drivers
There's a mole among your drivers
What lighter?
Screw you
You can't disqualify me
I only get to take the Gaokao once a year
I am the Game King
You're from a rich family
Not some refugee
This seems to be the same
Is this yours?
If we put our weight into it, won't it move?
Even the caged fish is handed over
You know your stuff
Then let's have this
They really like it
Let's have something crunchy
Be a home chef
Right?
We can make them some food
Marry a man like...
I, I, I... just take a look at me
It's about who you think is sleeping in yours
You just swap with them
I think Bro Ning is sleeping in mine
Then let's flip Bro Ning over, okay?
Hahaha
What do you mean flip big bro? I'll give you...
I'll give you an arm
Hold it, hold it, slow down
No rush
Let's Start Deduction can record 100G
3, 2
The second-to-last digit of the account
Boys are all odd numbers
Girls are all even numbers
Then I found this combination is actually very easy
Is it possible that it's like this?
For example, this mug of mine
If I just hit you with a glass,
You won't die
But after I fill it with two liters of water,
You'd die instantly
You can kill without entering the door
Awesome! Awesome!
So you mean you're sure he's dead?
So you don't need to delete the video, right?
No need to figure out the motive.
Everyone has a motive to kill.
And actually carried it out.
I've laid it all out so clearly for you.
I don't believe the body was already in Tunnel 1.
So how did he make sure the body wouldn't be found?
This thing was actually already turned on.
The boss would definitely have his phone with him.
That's for sure.
So earlier I wanted to say,
who's been to the boss's office?
Both of them have.
So it's between the two of them.
I'm telling you,
it's between the two of them.
Hey.
Wait a second.
What illness does Li Fei have?
Right, it's possible he exposed it on purpose.
So,
Li Fei is suspicious too.
I don't know why.
Why is it that none of you suspect him?
Why does no one suspect him? Why couldn't it be him?
He should...
He's acting very off.
He's been wandering around the whole time.
Since when does he ever just wander around?
The true culprit in this case is Ming Qipao.
Come on.
- We never lose when we team up. - Yeah.
Congratulations, bro.
Let's all congratulate our bro.